qualitysmith.com 2018-08-14

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy and Information Gathering

The privacy of our customers is extremely important to us. We work with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site (first party cookies). A cookie is a small packet of information stored on a user's computer that allows a website server to know certain information about a user, for example, how many times a user has visited the site. A web beacon is typically a transparent graphic placed on a site or in an email that allows a site to record, for example, whether a page was accessed or an e-mail opened, for statistical analysis. Our cookies and Web beacons are not tied to personally identifiable information. We don't collect personal information without your knowledge. We ask for it in a form that must be submitted by the user. 

We have agreements with certain data management platform companies and/or behavioral advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our websites. Behavioral advertising companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this ‘behavioral advertising' practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit the network advertising initiative's opt-out link at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

### Service From Third-Party Sites

We utilize trusted corporate partners for assistance in finding contractors in your area to serve you. At that point, you'll be notified of the name of that company and begin to receive e-mail and phone communications from them regarding your contractor choice. Once contacted by our corporate partner, you'll have the opportunity to opt out of their non-transactional e-mail and phone communications and your personal information will be governed by their privacy policy/terms and conditions. 

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by QualitySmith Inc. Please be aware that QualitySmith Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
